

## Profile

Experienced and reliable product manager with a good sense of design and full of creative ideas. I combine skills of product and business management and technical background of front-end development.

I'm happy to work with smart, open-minded people and to use modern technologies and methodologies. I like to propose and implement hypotheses, influence the development of a project, design a product, plan development paths, experiment, implement new opportunities, argue about new functions, come up with ways out of hopeless business situations, analyze.

# Employment History

# Product manager at TradingView, Rostov-on-Don

October 2018 - May 2019

In TradingView I worked as product manager, but also combined functions of project manager.

- Established key road-map themes. Determined which features to add to the road-map
- Led product team meetings, scrum meetings
- Managed backlogs and prioritized technical work
- Wrote user stories and defined requirements for design and engineering teams. Produced feature specifications. Drafted release notes for product launches
- Collaborated with design, engineering and marketing teams
- Monitored and optimized release cycle processes
- Worked with internal teams and stakeholders to generate ideas. Identified ideas that aligned with strategy. Explained why certain ideas were prioritized and others were not
- Analyzed product feedback and requests

# Product manager at GraphGrail (MySmartChat), Rostov-on-Don

July 2018 - August 2018

I have taken part in a product launch. The main part of my job was behavior analysis of early adopters. I conducted user interviews, collected and analyzed feedback. Wrote user stories, defined requirements for engineering team, generated and tested ideas, based on collected data.

Also, important thing was customer on-boarding, delivering product demos for new features — I captured short videos of functionality usage, described features and trained our support team and first users.

Besides this, I helped to search for investors and took part in negotiations.

In addition, we had no designer in team, so I made design prototypes too.

#### **Details**

Russia, +7-909-421-6222 nikitabuevich@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth

15.11.1992

Rostov-on-Don

Nationality

Russian

#### Links

Personal website

#### **Skills**

Product management

Agile Project Management

Knowledgable in User Interface/ User Experience

Frontend Development

#### **Hobbies**

Travelling. Black and white film photography. MtB, climbing, snowboard, wakeborad, surf. Arthouse movies, smart books.
Listening jazz. Drinking good wine and whiskey, eating tasty food.

#### Languages

Russian

English

## Frontend architect at GraphGrail (MySmartChat), Rostov-on-Don

January 2018 - July 2018

I came to MySmartChat (child project of GraphGrail) as contractor to help to choose suitable technologies, develop architecture of front-end and to make MVP. But the idea of project fascinated me and I stayed in it until the end.

After the core of prototype and UI-kit were developed, I counseled our HRs in front-end developers recruitment, interviewed. Then I was mentor for junior developers, realized code-review, controlled code-style and code quality.

#### Frontend consultant at AvtoTO, Rostov-on-Don

October 2016 - January 2018

I worked in AvtoTO as remote front-end consultant. The task was to make a redesign of online store.

Developed scope assessment, established key road-map themes. Staff recruitment counseling (designer, front-end developers) and interviewing. Supervised UI/UX design development. Helped to choose technologies, developed architecture of front-end and UI-kit. Mentored front-end developers, realized code-review, code-style and code quality control. Set up business processes.

#### Frontend developer at VezetVsem, Rostov-on-Don

April 2015 - August 2017

Worked as front-end developer, using such technologies as JS, React+flux, ES6, webpack, HTML, SCSS, BEM, jQuery. Closely collaborated with design team.

Also took part in generating and explanation of priority of ideas, analyzed product feedback and requests, was interested in business case justification.

When I got more experience, started to mentor junior developers and make codereview.

## Project manager at Plan B, Rostov-on-Don

September 2014 - January 2015

I worked as a partner with Plan B studio. I was responsible for the support of existing clients.

- Established key road-map themes. Determined which features to add to the road-map
- Managed backlogs and prioritized technical work
- Monitored and optimized release cycle processes
- Wrote user stories and defined requirements for design and engineering teams. Produced feature specifications. Drafted release notes for product launches
- Worked with internal teams and stakeholders to generate ideas. Identified ideas that aligned with strategy. Explained why certain ideas were prioritized and others were not
- Analyzed product feedback and requests
- Negotiated with clients
- Searched for contractors

#### CPO at 100% Sports, Rostov-on-Don

November 2012 - November 2013

I worked in a sport/extreme stuff shop "100% Sports". I was a head of the online store of this company and was responsible for the quality of service and for business metrics. I had a team of 5-10 (in different time) managers and other staff. During 1 year of my work the project's revenue increased 4 times.

# Own Projects

## Active recreation club "Katuha", Co-owner

October 2017 - May 2018

Rostov-on-Don

A small travel company that organizes holidays in the mountains (ski/snowboard, mtb, rafting, etc).

- Business strategy development; development and formalization of businessprocesses; financial planning
- · Marketing, SMM
- Team management (marketers, content-managers, tourism instructors, managers)
- Tours organization (negotiation with hotels, transport companies, tourism instructors, etc)

# Web studio "Dvigaidelo", Co-owner / CTO

February 2014 - April 2015

Rostov-on-Don

Together with a partner marketer we organized the small web studio. I was responsible for all aspects of business, connected with product development. During the year we have successfully implemented about 10 projects.

It was our first experience in business. Project has died because of financial problems (crisis of 2014) and our marketing mistake that we made a big bet on word mouth.

## Education

Bachelor Degree in Applied Math and Computer Science, Southern Federal University, Rostov-on-Don

September 2019 - June 2019

Assistant translator in Math and Computer Science, Southern Federal University, Rostov-on-Don

September 2019 - May 2019

#### Courses

Product Mindset, Program for the development of product thinking
February 2019 - April 2019

Academic art course, Art studio "Kolorit"

September 2005 - May 2009

# **◄** References

References available upon request